~~
Yes, that's right.
I went to this city, Chinatown.
Now, yes.
Today, you know, there is no staff
So, just us members
We're going to Motomachi Chinatown.
I'll see you there.
I'm looking forward to Chinatown.
Let's eat choufu together.
I've never had choufu.
You haven't? Then let's eat it.
We've never been to Chinatown before, have we?
First time.
Ready, set, go!
Okay, let's go.
Oh, hey.
We're in the restaurant.
Oh, we're all eating together?
We're having shoo-dofu, right, guys?
Yes, we'll eat.
Yes, we will eat it.
But the choux... Oh, I see.
How many do you want?
But this one, right?
But four of these.
Two of these?
I know, right? Oh, man.
No, I'm good. I'm good.
Two for me, two for everyone.
Okay.
We'll be waiting.
Ta-da!
Looks delicious!
This is the place where you can eat and drink.
But, I mean, can you eat your way through it?
Bon appétit!
This is it, right?
Yes, thank you.
It's hot. Be careful.
Soda soup.
It's hot. Inside.
Oh, seriously, the juice.
You have to break the juice, sure.
You gotta drain it. I mean, you gotta drain it.
Is this green tea flavor? This one.
Just the skin.
What is that?
No?
Seafood. Seafood.
It's so hot.
How is it?
It's good.
It's great.
We're going to need more.
You've eaten here before?
Yes, I've eaten here before.
It's really good, isn't it?
Yeah, it's really good.
When I came here alone, I ate outside by myself.
He said something about coming alone.
How's he doing?
She looked sad by herself.
I think so.
He was really sad.
The juice tastes good, doesn't it?
Yeah, it's good.
I said it tastes good.
Hmm?
I said it's good.
It's good.
Yummy.
It's what?
It's good.
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yummy.
You mean it's good?
It's good.
Okay, well, try it.
Can I try it?
Okay, then.
Can you please remove the steam?
You can't see the steam.
Looks good.
I don't see any steam.
Do you ever see the steam?
Yes, it does.
Looks so good!
I got it.
Looks so good! Looks so good!
Oh, my God!
Wow!
Wow, the steam is so hot!
Looks so good!
Se-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no-no
I'm so scared!
It's so hot!
Se
I'm so scared!
Let him get to his own body temperature.
Se-no!
Let him go
Let it go
Let it go! Let it go!
Let's go!
Se's
Delicious!
What kind of fried rice is this?
It's Chinese.
Chinese.
It's so good.
It's good.
Bon appétit.
Bon appétit. - Bon appétit. - Bon appétit.
We have a lot of things here.
Sesame dumplings.
Ah!
Chinese pickles.
This is called "Chinese pickles.
Chinese pickles, right?
Sesame dumplings! How polite!
What?
Sesame dumplings are so polite!
Look at this.
Wow!
Wontan noodles.
Oh no!
Try it!
Is it that close? Camera.
Oh, excuse me.
Look.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Yeah. - Okay.
I'll eat.
How do you like it?
Spicy?
Not spicy.
These noodles...
Yes, sir.
That's it.
Reminds me of a high bar.
Wow, nice.
Okay.
I'm going to have a private dinner now.
Yes, we are.
Yes, ma'am.
I'd love to.
You look so full.
I am.
What did you enjoy?
Sesame dumplings.
What was good?
Daikon radish rice cake.
Yes, I did.
Where would you like to go next?
Cosmo World.
Yes, sir.
Let's go to Cosmo World.
I'd like to go to Cosmo World.
Cosmo World?
It's an amusement park.
Amusement park.
Okay.
Then let's go to the next one.
Let's go.
Ready, go!
So, there's something I'd like to do now.
Yes, what is it?
Yesterday, actually, you asked if the four of us had any questions.
So that's what we're talking about.
Yes, I do.
So, as we head to Cosmo World
I'd like to answer a few questions.
Yes, sir.
Okay, 24 minutes left.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Okay, I'm going.
Wow, I don't know what to do.
Okay, we've got a lot of time, so let's just answer as many as we can.
Okay, then.
What do you admire about each other?
None.
One. One each.
Wow, that sucks.
Yes, sir.
That's the worst.
OK, the leader is aesthetically conscious
He's very conscious about everything.
Yes, sir.
And Am...
Delicious. Last one.
Am...
I don't think so.
No, it's not.
No, no, no.
No, no.
I'm a very visual person.
I'm very visual.
Very much.
Ishi is tall.
Tall.
Only
Only.
Then we are, let's see...
Well, first of all, Ici is...
When it comes to performance
Oh, my God.
It's like...
It's like, "Oh, my God, I'm going to do it again.
So, Amu-kun...
You know what?
I'm serious.
I don't know...
You're amazing.
He's good at expressing his feelings.
That's for sure.
What's your enthusiasm for the show?
That's a long story.
Why?
You're the leader, so you're very passionate about it.
No, not really.
Hey, what's up, Amu?
Why were you cut?
Ishi...
I don't know, I just...
Produce your own
Promotion
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm really good at it.
So I feel like I know myself very well.
I know myself very well.
When you see the red brick warehouse
Here we go.
Wait, we ran here.
Did you run?
Yes, I ran.
Yes, you did.
Oh, Eechi.
Oh, I think we might have run together.
I might have run with you out of nowhere.
Oh, we already ran.
But we passed the Red Brick Warehouse.
Somebody.
Eechi went by.
I think it's Eechi.
It's backlit now. It's very emo.
Let's shoot the opening right here.
Oh, that's good.
Okay.
Oh, okay, that's good.
Because there's gotta be four of us.
Okay, then.
Okay, so, Isshin moves three.
Okay.
I'll come out last.
I'm going to come out at the end.
I mean, it doesn't have to be an opening.
What?
Whatever.
Samnee? Thumbnail?
Thumbnail... Oh, let's use this as a thumbnail.
I was looking that way. I was looking that way.
Twilight.
That's cool.
Okay.
Ok.
What's the one thing you've found recently that has made you like any of the members?
Wow, huh?
Haruma is kind of central to the group.
Uh-huh.
So that's pretty much it. We're kind of a team.
That's for sure.
For this group, it's really
I'm grateful
I feel like it's for the better.
Yeah, it's great.
We're almost at Cosmo World.
What's at Cosmo World?
It's an amusement park.
There's Cosmo World.
Are there rides and stuff?
Does it have a roller coaster?
Can you ride a roller coaster? Everyone can.
Yes, you can.
But you'll regret it.
I'll be careful.
Wow.
22nd and up.
Too soft
It's too soft.
What?
Is it still on? This is it.
Meeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee
Yes, sir.
Bye-bye!